Preliminary guide to the James Goode papers, Circa 1860-2018 MS0670.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, slides and awards, circa 1860-2009; Series 5; 16.5 Linear Feet
  - Photographs, circa 1860-2009; Series 5 Subseries 1
    - Family Granny Browne (great grandmother), Undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - James Goode's great grandparents, circa 1890; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - James Goode's grandfather, 1896; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - James Goode family, circa 1900-circa 1930; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Personal photographs, circa 1900-circa 1960; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      Includes school/childhood, family, and vacation photographs. Original order maintained.
    - Personal photographs, circa 1910-circa 1985; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - James Goode's uncle, circa 1915; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Family photos, circa 1920-circa 1980; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      Found loose in a box with no original order. Unidentified.
    - James Goode's mother and father, circa 1928-circa 1930; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - James Goode's aunt and uncle, circa 1935; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - James Goode's cousin's wedding, 1938; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Personal photos, circa 1940; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Personal photographs, circa 1940-circa 1970; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Personal photographs, circa 1940-circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      Found loose in a box with no original order. Mostly unidentified.
    - Personal photographs, circa 1940-circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Family Photo, Circa 1940; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - James Goode, 6th birthday party, 1945; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - James Goode, age 8, 1948; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Confederate parade, 1962; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Personal photographs, circa 1950-circa 1970; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Personal photographs, circa 1950- circa 1970; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Personal photographs, circa 1950-circa 1970; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Architecture negatives and slides, circa 1950-circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - James Goode, age 11, 1951; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - James Goode, age 12, 1951; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Empire vases, 1954; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Goode family reunion, 1954; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Hickory, NC, 1954; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - North Carolina, 1954; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - North Carolina, 1954; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Hickory, NC house, 1955; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - James Goode family, 1955; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - James Goode family, 1955; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - James Goode family, 1955; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - North Carolina, 1955; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Wilmington, NC city fire boat, 1955; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - North Carolina, 1956; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - James Goode, Hickory High School, NC, 1957; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - James Goode Hickory High School, NC graduation photo, 1957; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - North Carolina, 1957; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - UNC YMCA Camp, Camp New Hope, 1957; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Item 1)
    - Family photo, Sedgefield, NC, 1958; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Negatives, 1960; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 20)
      Found loose in a box. Unidentified.
    - Personal photographs, circa 1960-circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 21)
      Found loose in a box. Includes architecture and personal photographs.
    - Photo album, US Army in Germany, Cape Cod, MA, and Alexandria, VA, 1960-1966; Series 5 (Box 41, Item 19)
    - Photographs, circa 1960-circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Vacation photos, circa 1960-circa 1970; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 23)
      This and the next two folders were found together in one envelope. The folders include photographs of Germany, Austria, South Carolina architecture and and streets, and Kentucky.
    - Vacation photos, circa 1960-circa 1970; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Vacation photos, circa 1960-1970; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Negatives and contact sheets, circa 1960; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Goode photos and family history, circa 1960-circa 1995; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Architecture negatives and contact sheets, circa 1965-1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      Includes photographs of Virginia and Maryland and were found loose in a box with no order.
    - North Carolina and University of Virginia photographs, 1966-1968; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Personal photographs, 1967; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Whig Society at George Mason College, 1967; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Alexandria, VA photographs, 1967-1968; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Personal and architecture photos, circa 1970-circa 2000; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      Photographs in this and the next folder were found in the same envelope.
    - Personal and architecture photos, circa 1970-circa 2000; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Smithsonian Women's Committee auction, 1974; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Hillwood Estate, 1975; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Woodrow Wilson Center lecture, 1979; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Carriage gate to Smithsonian Castle, circa 1980; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Capital losses publications party, circa 1980; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Visit to Jaspar, TX, 1980; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Personal photos, circa 1980-circa 2000; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Personal photographs, circa 1980-circa 2000; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Personal photos, circa 1980-circa 2000; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - James Goode visit to Constantine Sofalio (?), circa 1983; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - James Goode with President Reagan, circa 1983; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Smithsonian Castle academic procession, 1983; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Smithsonian mace, 1983; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - St. Mary's City, Maryland, circa 1985; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Postcard photo album, 1985-1995; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Item 2)
      Inscribed: "Miscellaneous post cards collected by James Goode, 1985-1995, mostly historic houses but also what ever struck my fancy, especially unusual and bizarre cards."
    - Personal and architecture photos, circa 1985-2000; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      These photographs were found loose in a box. None are identified.
    - Personal photo negatives, circa 1985-circa 2000; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Literary Society of Washington, DC, circa 1986; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Smithsonian Renwick Gallery, 1986; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Trip to Shenandoah, 1986; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - James Goode, circa 1987; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Personal photographs, 1987; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      These photographs were in a folder labeled "photos - 1987", but the photos themselves are labeled 2/3/93. All are unidentified.
    - State photographs, 1987-1988; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      This and Box 100, Folder 8 come from the same binder. The folders include photographs, negatives, and slides of Delaware, New Jersey, Maryland, California, Tennessee, New Mexico, Florida, Washington, DC, North Carolina, and South Carolina.
    - State photographs, 1987-1988; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Bar Harbor, ME, circa 1988; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Trip to San Diego, CA, 1989; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Drive from DC to Key West, FL, 1989; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Architecture photos, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Architecture trip to New Jersey, 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Homewood, Baltimore, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Personal photographs, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      This folder includes vacation photographs from California and Oregon as well as photographs of friends, various events, and miscellaneous architecture.
    - Personal photographs, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Sotterly Plantation, Maryland, circa 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Library of Congress, 1990; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Visit to Galveston and other Texan towns, 1991; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Alexandria, VA dinner party, Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - James Goode visits Breckingridge, circa 1995; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Rehoboth Beach, DE, 1995; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Ruthmere estate, Indiana, 1995; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Slide lecture on Thomas Ustick Walter, 1995; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Eastern Virginia historic houses, 1996; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Visiting Daniel Maxfield in Key West, FL, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - James Goode Washington, DC apartment, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Florida photos and slides, 1997-2001; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Key West, FL; visiting David Maxfield, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Key West photographs, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Key West photographs, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - New Castle, DE, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Backyard of my house; book shop in New Castle, Dela., 1998; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Neumours, Wilmington, DE, 1998; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Annapolis, 1999; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Interior of my house; bookshop in New Castle, Dela., 1999; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Attending the horse race, Winterthur, DE, 1999; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Storm aftermath in New Castle, Dela., 1999; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Farewell party for Tom Doherty, 1999; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Florida photos, 2001; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      These are personal vacation photographs and many are identified
    - Photograph album Key West, FL [1/3], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Photograph album Key West, FL [2/3], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Photograph album, Key West FL [3/3], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Negatives Key West, FL, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Richard Homeland birthday, 2006; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Homewood, Baltimore, 2006; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Hay-Adams Hotel "Welcome to Our Historic Neighborhood" pamphlets, 2007; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Renovation of the Kennedy Warren Apartment House, 2009; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Family photos, undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Item 3)
    - Family portrait, undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Item 4)
    - Negatives, undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Photo album, used book store and their owners and vintage cards, undated; Series 5, Subseries 1 (Box 41, Item 20)
    - Photograph album (2), 1950-1959; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Item 19)
    - Photograph album (3), circa 1942; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Item 20)
    - Photo Album, 1997-2000; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Antique bowl, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - ABDY Valentine (Paris photos), Undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Antique sign, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Slides, circa 1958-1999; Series 5 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains more than 500 color slides. The subject matter includes vacations, family, and architecture. The slides range in date from circa 1958-1999.
    - Small grey slide box, circa 1958; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Item 1)
      Includes approximately 30 slides of Augusta, GA.
    - Architecture slides, circa 1970; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Italy and Kiev slides, 1971; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - International travel slides, circa 1975; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Russia slides, 1975; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Oak Knoll and New Castle slides, 1998-1999; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Architecture slides, undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Architecture slides, undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Blue slide box, undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Item 2)
      The box includes approximately 125 slides of historic houses, including Rockwood, Odessa Corbit House, and Read House.
    - Grey slide box, undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Item 3)
      This box includes approximately 300 slides of various architectural sites in England.
  - Photographs, awards. degrees, 1964-2018; Series 5 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains framed photographs, diplomas, and awards presented to James Goode. The materials range in date from 1964-2017.
    Arranged in no particular order
    - Photograph, James Goode shaking hands with Dr. Billington, circa 1978; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Photograph, home of Dr. William Seale (Barthonew Cox, William Murtaugh, Lucinda Seale, and James Goode pictured), circa 1990; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Photograph, James Goode, Mrs. Ernest Preston, and Woodrow Reagan, circa 1990; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Photograph, 50th Birthday party of William Seale (Mrs. Robert Montagne, Mr. Robert Montagne, and two other pictured), 08/1998; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Photograph, reception at the White House meeting President and Mrs. Reagan, circa 1986; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Photograph, James Goode and Tom Dougharty, outdoors, New Castle, DE, 08/1998; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Photograph, Mrs. Dorothy Goode (mother of James Goode), circa 1955; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Three Centuries of the American Bookplate, 2010; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Cincinnati Society certificate of membership, 2017; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Award, Stanford White Award presented by Patterson House Preservation Fund, 1964; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Award, Award of Merit presented by the American Association for State and Local History, 2004; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - BA diploma, James Goode, University of South Carolina, 1964; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Print and pamphlet, James Goode and Company Architectural Books Catalog 3, 1998; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Masters degree diploma, James Goode, University of Virginia, 1966; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Ph.D. diploma, James Goode, George Washington University, 1995; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Award, Clariosophic Literary Society, 1964; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Framed award, Award of Merit presented by the American Association for State and Local History, 1990; Series 5 (Box 40, Item 15)
    - Framed award, presented by the Historical Society of Washington, DC, 1992; Series 5 (Box 40, Item 16)
    - Framed award, presented by the Friends of Cast-Iron Architecture, 1979; Series 5 (Box 40, Item 17)
    - Framed award, presented by the Jefferson Society of the University of Virginia, 1966; Series 5 (Box 40, Item 18)
    - Ripley, S. Dillon, 1988; Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Goode Awards, 2008-2017; Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Awards Washington Post, 1989; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Awards Washington Chapter of AIA, 2008; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 117, Folder 25)
    - Award Presentation DVDs, 2015; Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Historical Society Wash. D.C., 2015; Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Certificate of Appreciation, 2013; Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Award for Excellence in Historic Presentation, 2017; Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Awards presentation, 2017; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Awards University of Virginia, 2018; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 117, Folder 13)
- Personal papers, 1903-2017; 1950-2014; Series 6; 4 Linear Feet
  Arranged by like material and chronologically
  The materials of this series include diaries, checking account ledgers, telephone and address books, appointment books, newspapers, a baby book, school papers, and other personal records. They range in date from 1903 to 2014, but the bulk of the material dates from 1950 to 1998. These are the personal papers of James Goode.
  - Papers saved of Grandfather Wagg (?) from his desk at his death, 1939; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Baby book, 1939-1944; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Claremont College Herald, Hickory NC, 1903; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Confederate song, undated; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Personal papers, circa 1940-circa 1950; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Old school papers, 1945-1955; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - School report cards, 1950s; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper grammar school, 1952; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Library card, 1953; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers junior high school, 1953; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers junior high school, 1954; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers junior high school, 1955; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - High school magazine, 1955-1956; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - High school plays, 1957; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Hickory, NC, High School Class of 1957, Series 6 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Principals of Hickory, NC schools, 1957; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - High school graduation, 1957; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - High school diploma, 1957; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Voice recording, 1957; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Army papers, 1958-1961; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Army records, 1958; Series 6 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Antique dealers, Capitol Hill, 1967; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Drivers license DC, 1969; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Mental illness case of aunt Eliz. Simons, 1977; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Dinner Renwick Gallery, 1980; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Vacation plans, 1980s; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Washingtonian of the Year, 1989; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Invitation, Saul, 1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Christmas cards sent, 1998-2003; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Christmas cards received (favorites), 1999-2006; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1957; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Diary, 1957-1958; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Journal, 1958-1959; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Diary, 1959-1960; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Diary, 1959-1960; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Diary, 1961-1962; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Travel jounral, 1961; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1962-1964; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Journal, 1964-1966; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1966-1970; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Journal, 1970-1974; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Short diary and check ledger, 1975-1978; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Diary and check ledger, 1977-1978; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Business ledger, 1971-1974; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Check ledger, 1975-1976; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Checking account ledger, 1979-1980; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Account for checking, 1980-1982; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Checking account ledger, 1982-1984; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Banking ledger, 1984-1985; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Checking account ledger, 1985-1987; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Checking account ledger, 1987-1989; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Check ledger, 1990-1991; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Checking account, 1991-1998; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Inventory of antique furnishings, 01/1988; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Telephone log, 1988-1991; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Telephone log, 1991-1996; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Telephone log, 1996-1998; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Address and phone books, 1964-1966; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - 5 telephone books, 1966-1969; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - 7 telephone books, 1970-1974; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - 5 address/telephone books, 1974-1978; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - 3 address/telephone books, 1979-1980; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 3 address/telephone books, 1982-1985; Series 6 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - 4 address/telephone books, 1985-1990; Series 6 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - 3 address/telephone books, 1990-1994; Series 6 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - 4 address books, 2000-2006; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - 4 address books, 2006-2013; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Address book, 2009; Series 6 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Appointment books, 1971-1974; Series 6 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Appointment books, 1975-1978; Series 6 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Appointment books, 1979-1980; Series 6 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Appointment books, 1981-1984; Series 6 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Appointment books, 1985-1987; Series 6 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Appointment books, 1988-1990; Series 6 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Appointment books, 1991-1993; Series 6 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Appointment books, 1994-1997; Series 6 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Appointment books, 2010-2013; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Appointment books, 2013-2014; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Appointment book, 2015; Series 6 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - First day cover stamp collection, circa 1955; Series 6 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Obituary, mother, undated; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - CD - Birch, Decatur, Dougal, Walsh-McLean, Undated; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - 2 VHS Tapes "Interview - Self Portrait Exhibition" and "The Stone Carvers", 1985-1993; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Small Collection Plans, 2013; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Small Exhibits, 2014; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Jamestowne Society, 2017; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - RR Articles, 2017; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 15)